maxbupa.com 2014-11-22

# We are Keen in Maintaining our Privacy Policy!

## Max Bupa is committed to protecting your privacy and information of confidential nature which may become known to it while you visit and/or use this website.

Max Bupa collects personal information in accordance with the applicable laws and is committed to take all reasonable precautions to preserve the integrity and prevent any corruption or loss, damage or destruction of the data and information. All medical information will be kept confidential and may only be disclosed to those involved with your treatment or care, or organization, which may be responsible for meeting your treatment expenses, or their agents. The information may be shared with an external organization if the same is necessary to enable Max Bupa to provide you services or to enable the compilation of a transaction, credit reporting, or the same is necessary or required pursuant to applicable insurance norms or pursuant to the terms and conditions applicable to such information as agreed to with Max Bupa. Needless to add, confidentiality norms as applicable shall be adhered. Max Bupa does not check, edit or reveal it to any third parties except where it believes in good faith, such action is necessary to comply with the applicable legal and regulatory processes or to protect its own rights and interests. Max Bupa also reserves the right to perform statistical analyses on the data and information without indentifying any individual to understand user behavior and characteristics and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. Max Bupa will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

Max Bupa may use "cookies" (Cookies are small data files that a website stores on your computer.) for storing visitor preferences, profiling visitors and tracking visitor behavior on this website. By visiting this website you acknowledge, accept and expressly authorize Max Bupa for the placement of cookies on your computer.

Safeguards to Customers Personal and/or sensitive Information* :

We assure you that Max Bupa has a comprehensive documented information security programme and information security policies that contain managerial, technical, operational and physical security control measures that are commensurate with the information assets being protected with the nature of business.

## Authorization for Use of Personal and/or Sensitive Information :

You consent to and authorize Max Bupa, and /or any of its authorized representatives to seek or obtain any personal information from you in respect of its rendered services, such as medical information from any hospital/medical practitioner that you or any person proposed to be insured has attended or may attend in future concerning any disease or illness or injury.

You further consent to and authorize Max Bupa to use and disclose any personal information collected or available with it (whether contained in this proposal form or otherwise obtained) to its underwriting personnel, claims investigation companies/agencies/service providers and insurance/reinsurance companies as is necessary and required for the purpose of processing of this proposal form, providing subsequent services in relation to the policy and processing of claims under the policy.

Max Bupa assures you that Max Bupa or any person on its behalf holding your sensitive personal data or information shall not retain that information for longer than is required for the purposes for which the information may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under any other law

At any time while availing the services or otherwise, You also have an option to withdraw this consent given such withdrawal of the consent shall be sent in writing to us. In such a case where you are withdrawing the consent, We reserve rights of not providing any further services for which the said information was sought.

However, You have an option to review the information you have provided and ensure that any personal information or sensitive personal data or information if found to be inaccurate or deficient may be corrected or amended as feasible. Wherein, we shall not be responsible for the authenticity of the personal.

If you have any questions or queries, please send us an e-mail at the following address:

* The Sensitive personal data or information should mean as defined under the IT rules 2011
